(Heaven's Dao is in turmoil.)
(As Empress Dowager Chen passed away,)
(the late emperor Xiao Nandu reclaims
the throne,)
(making Lu Zhen'er the Empress,)
(and imprisoning
the new emperor Xiao Wenjing.)
(Lu Zhen'er suddenly awaked)
(and resolved to end
the turmoil herself.)
Come on. If you want to leave, hurry up.
If you don't, you can't stay.
Don't force me to act.
I don't want to see any of you
in this palace.
Take blank imperial edicts.
Write whatever you want.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
May you rise above all others.
Okay.
- May you success.
- Thank you.
- May you be beautiful and wealthy.
- I will.
May your wishes come true.
Come on.
Long life Your Majesty.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Stop fanning.
Just go, all of you.
Yes.
Just go.
All of you, leave.
Everyone, leave now.
If you want to leave, hurry up.
I can't control you.
You're disgraceful!
Get out!
My father will be sad
to see you like this.
I don't want to see you.
Stop this.
Lu,
look, I'm also a deer.
I made it myself.
I sneaked a bite.
Shall I feed you?
I'm not sweet-talking you.
I want to reconcile.
Don't speak to me with that face.
He never speaks to me that way.
(Why am I sad again?)
Will Lu Zhen'er come today?
Ever since Empress Dowager Chen died,
Lu Zhen'er has gone mad!
This chaos has been lasting for a month.
When will it end?
She's here.
Here she comes again.
How dare she behave in court!
Utterly disgraceful!
You!
Horse!
How dare you!
Your Majesty fall in love with me,
a wild horse.
Then I'll gallop across your palaces
like a green pasture!
You overstep!
If you continue like this,
do not blame me for being ruthless.
I'd like to see how ruthless you can be.
Don't think I'll indulge you forever.
So I intend to see
where your limit lies.
Absurd!
I know you care for Xiao Wenjing.
If you dare act recklessly again,
then Xiao Wenjing's life
won't be saved.
Zhen'er,
choose wisely.
=His Chosen Favor=
(You! Horse)
=Episode 22=
Why?
Why is everything gone?
Where is the real Xiao Wenjing?
Has his past
been erased?
Xiao Wenjing,
can you come back?
(Lu Zhen'er, I know this isn't you.)
What is this?
(Lu Zhen'er, late emperor's consort)
Don't sleep.
Kneel!
I told you to kneel!
If you refuse,
fine,
I'll destroy my face.
Let's see how that useless one reacts
when she comes back.
Don't think I won't kill you.
Go ahead, kill me.
If you kill me,
she'll never return.
Don't harm her.
I'll kneel.
(I don't know where you are,)
(but I know)
(you don't want to see this.)
(So I've decided)
(to trade myself for your return.)
Where is the former Lu Zhen'er?
If you don't answer me,
I'll kill myself right now.
(Her will is weak.)
(She's lost her qualification
as the heroine.)
(The main world believes
the original Lu Zhen'er)
(is a better choice for the heroine.)
How is her will weak?
(She's too emotional)
(and indecisive,)
(so unfit to be the heroine.)
So your definition of a heroine
is the heartless,
and cold-blooded woman,
who is alone
and only cares about herself,
just like current Lu Zhen'er
who treats lives like dirt?
(This isn't my judgment,)
(but the comments captured by big data.)
A heroine must first be a living person.
This is my comic.
She's my absolute protagonist.
No matter who you are,
give her back to me.
(If the host wants Lu Zhen'er
back to this world,)
(fine.)
(As long as the host makes a deal,)
(she will return.)
What is it?
(Because the host interfered
with the main storyline,)
(making Lu Zhen'er fall in love
with you,)
(she was erased by the main world.)
(Trade your soul,)
(and she'll return.)
My soul?
(After losing your original soul,)
(you'll be lost in this world forever,)
(becoming the real Xiao Wenjing.)
Then will she come back?
(Yes.)
I want her back.
So,
I can return
because of Xiao Wenjing.
Xiao Wenjing,
(Xiao Wenjing,)
(even if you've forgotten me,)
(I won't give up.)
(I will awaken you.)
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, what can I do for you?
I need to speak with you.
Speak your mind, Your Majesty.
Qing'er isn't an outsider.
Your Majesty,
I shall take my leave now.
(So obedient.)
(Seems the bewitching consort taught her
a harsh lesson.)
Your Majesty,
what do you wish to say?
You're afraid of me?
Just speak plainly, Your Majesty.
In broad daylight,
we are alone together,
which is improper.
Do you not remember me?
You are my father's wife.
Physical contact with me
is inappropriate.
Xiao Wenjing,
I'm your beloved.
Do you remember?
Please watch your words.
It's alright.
Fine if you can't remember.
He'll remember eventually.
(So what if he forgets?)
(Instinct reveals the truth.)
(He still cares for me.)
Why do you obey
your father unquestioningly?
Naturally, a son obeys his father.
I'm your mother,
so you should obey me.
What do you want me to do?
What did he order you to do?
I'm speaking to you.
Why aren't you answering?
He ordered me to conceive
a child with Qing'er.
Why would he make the order?
For elixir.
For elixir?
What kind of elixir?
The elixir of immortality.
He needs umbilical blood
from a close relative.
Why doesn't he father one?
He can't?
I don't know.
Don't go yet.
You love my father, right?
I don't love him.
I love you.
So from now on,
you will only listen to me.
You'll do whatever I tell you to do.
Do you understand?
This is improper.
From this moment forward,
you will only love me, cherish me,
and obey me.
Don't bully me
and make me mad.
If others bully me, defend me.
If others insult me, argue for me.
Your heart and eyes must hold only me.
Understand?
♪Spring comes late after the snow♪
What
are you doing?
You unfilial son! You wretch!
Let go of me!
♪Spring comes late after the snow♪
♪Having endured sorrow and joy♪
♪Wandering the streets,
the story unfinished♪
♪Turning around, I lost you♪
♪Separated by the dust of the past♪
♪Our reunion veiled by moonlight♪
♪Grant me indifference or tenderness♪
♪Crowds push past, brushing shoulders♪
♪Love grows wild within the soul♪
♪Longing weaves into a net♪
♪Dare not speak, dare not gaze♪
♪Yet I crave your glance♪
♪Time, leaving many pasts behind♪
♪Desolation follows splendor♪
♪Only after seeing enough
worldly absurdity♪
♪Will I kiss your face♪
♪Never forgotten, hope you've been well♪
♪Borrowing the first ray
of spring light♪
♪Can it bring about for us?♪
♪One look back,
lasting till the end of time♪
♪Love grows wild within the soul♪
♪Longing weaves into a net♪
♪Dare not speak, dare not gaze♪
♪Yet I crave your glance♪
♪Time, leaving many pasts behind♪
♪Desolation follows splendor♪
♪Only after seeing enough
worldly absurdity♪
♪Will I kiss your face♪